Sky view, let's go into welding.
Chose welding, we see introduction to welding.
That's great.
And that zooms us in there.
And let's sort by name and choose some others.
Actually, let's go to intro, introduction.
Introduction, intro to welding repair.
We're going to stay away from that because it's auto.
And we'll come back to it later.
And introduction to metalworking.
Let's see, we want just welding.
We'll go introduction to welding.
Whoops, I just lost introduction to welding.
Where did it go?
Introduction to welding.
Now I have to go down here again.
You see how it jumped and I lost my place.
And so we've got that.
And then we'll keep this one.
There we go.
Jumping again, driving me nuts.
And then we'll go with that.
And we'll have to scroll back down.
Extra welding and fabrication.
I think we'll go with that.
And keep going.
Introduction to welding theory.
We'll go to introduction to principles and practices.
Let's leave it at that.
And then we'll click.
If I click enter, it, I'm not sure what it does.
But I'm not, I guess it threw those all up here.
That's fine.
But it leaves this up.
And after I click enter, I really think it should close this,
even though we made a prior decision on that.
So I'm going to click out of it to close it.
And then I'm going to fit all.
I like that, I like that choice very nice.
Okay, now I'm looking for the most prominent
of the introduction to welding.
It looks like it's this one.
But when I, when I put my cursor on it,
there it is right there.
Okay, so it seems like the anywhere I'm touching,
well, let's not get too picky.
Okay, so there's introduction to welding.
When I click on it, it expands nicely.
And I see introduction to welding.
When I hover over it and click it.
If I double click it, it should open the exhibit, right?
And it doesn't.
It opens this prototype V1.
And there's no way for me to get back now to sky view.
I have lost sky view.
I am stuck.
I tried going here.
When I go to sky view, it's going to reset sky view.
It's going to eliminate all of that.
The welding choices I made,
and it's going to, and I have to start all over.
So let's see, maybe I could go back here
to discipline and subjects.
Now I'm, now I'm over here in no man's land.
And let's go back to sky view.
And there we go.
Now we're stuck.
Okay, so we got in that little loop.
That's not all that I was going to explain.
There are other things.
Let me just very quickly go into one more
that I was going to, let's just choose anything.
Let's go back to intro,
intro.
Now this is sorting by,
it's sorting by best match, I guess.
Okay, introduction to,
let's go, introduction to welding.
Back to introduction to welding.
Introduction to welding.
Get back down here to welding and safety.
It's just little UI bugs we need to fix
for welding and welding safety.
And let's go to that.
And let's click out of it somewhere here.
And there we are.
So when I put my cursor over a mem,
let's go to this one where it's a nice big one.
For some reason when I click on this one now
it doesn't open up like it did before.
I don't know why.
Clicking different areas around it.
And don't know why.
I'm not, I guess these are,
I don't know, these are related,
these are standalone orbits.
Okay, that's fine.
We'll deal with that.
Let's just zoom in here a little more.
And here we are back on this.
When I click on it, nothing changes.
If I go over to Fullerton right here,
this weld 100, which seems to be a part,
it's coming from this star.
It doesn't, the hover over does not change.
The, it should say weld 100 Fullerton,
you know, two, three units.
And if I double click on it,
it should show me the exhibit
or the job, the course outline
or at least on this hover over,
give me the definite, the course description.
And it doesn't.
So it just shows this general welding.
If I go over here, oh, I see.
Okay, got you.
There it is.
Okay.
You know what?
My bad.
Forget everything I said there.
It's not a problem.
There it is.
And if we click on it,
it even shoots over here.
That's very nice.
And that looks really good.
Let's see what happens if I double click on it.
Ah, back stranded.
Okay.
All right.
Let's stop there.
I was going to try and drag
and drop another intro to welding course over to this,
which wasn't working for me,
but I'm now stranded back on the general sky view
and it would take too long.
So let's just stop it right there.